{
    "subject": "resource/Chrysostome_Liausu",
    "predicate": "property/deathPlace",
    "object": "Valpara\u00edso, Chile",
    "human_readable": "Chrysostome Liausu died in Valpara\u00edso, Chile.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9175223708152771,
            "question": "Was Chrysostome Liausu from Valpara\u00edso?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8543280959129333,
            "question": "Where did Chrysostome Liausu die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7856001853942871,
            "question": "When did Chrysostome Liausu die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7216260433197021,
            "question": "Are there any notable figures who also died in Valpara\u00edso?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6950078010559082,
            "question": "Who was Chrysostome Liausu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4236510097980499,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Chrysostome Liausu's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4114968180656433,
            "question": "What country is Valpara\u00edso located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40631386637687683,
            "question": "What is the significance of Valpara\u00edso, Chile?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3957710564136505,
            "question": "What was Chrysostome Liausu's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2863211929798126,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Chrysostome Liausu's family?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Chrysostome Liausu died in Valpara\u00edso, Chile.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2298_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Chrysostome Liausu's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2298_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of Valpara\u00edso, Chile?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2298_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Valpara\u00edso located in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2298_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2298_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2298_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2298_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2298_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2298_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2298_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2298_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2298_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2298_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2298_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states that Chrysostome Liausu died in the sea off the Malvinas (Falkland Islands) in March 1843, not in Valpara\u00edso, Chile. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the documents, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe document with file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2298/re-ranker-msmarco/13.txt mentions LIAUSU Charles-AUguste (R.P. Chrysostome, s.s.c.c.) and states that he was born on 13 March 1807 and died in 1839, but there is no information about his place of death being Valpara\u00edso, Chile."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context information mentions that R.P. LIAUSU Chrysostome died on July 5, 1839, but it specifies the location as \"Valparaiso\" and notes he was the Prefect apostolique of Southern Oceania, which does not indicate his death in Valpara\u00edso, Chile specifically. Therefore, the statement that Chrysostome Liausu died in Valpara\u00edso, Chile is not supported by the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Chrysostome Liausu died on September 5, 1839, but Valparaiso was not established as a city until 1843.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "He died on September 5, 1839, and context information states that he was Prefect Apostolic of Southern Oceania.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the original text states \"06-07 R.P.  LIAUSU Chrysostome, Pr\u00e9fet apostolique d\u2019Oc\u00e9anie du Sud \u00e0 Valparaiso.\", but also mentions \"D\u00e9c\u00e8s : 05/09/1839\", which indicates that Liausu died in September 1839, and not later on in another location.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information states that Chrysostome Liausu died on 5 September 1839, and specifically mentions his death place as \"Valparaiso\" without indicating it was a different Valpara\u00edso from Chile. It does not provide any evidence to suggest he died elsewhere.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}